♪♪
♪I want you to know ♪
♪that I'm happy for you ♪
♪I wish nothing but ♪
♪the best for you both ♪
♪An older version of me ♪
♪Is she perverted like me ♪
♪Would she go down on you in a theatre ♪
♪Does she speak eloquently ♪
♪And would she have your baby ♪
♪I'm sure she'd make a really excellent mother ♪
♪'Cause the love that you gave that we made ♪
♪wasn't able to make it enough for you to be open wide, ♪
♪And every time you speak her name ♪
♪Does she know how you told me you'd hold me ♪
♪Until you died, 'til you died ♪
♪But you're still alive ♪
♪And I'm here ♪
♪to remind you ♪
♪Of the mess you left when you went away ♪
♪It's not fair ♪
♪to deny me ♪
♪Of the cross I bear that you gave to me ♪
♪You, you, you oughta know ♪
♪You seem very well, ♪
♪things look peaceful ♪
♪I'm not quite as well, ♪
♪I thought you should know ♪
♪Did you forget about me Mr. Duplicity ♪
♪I hate to bug you in the middle of dinner ♪
♪It was a slap in the face ♪
♪how quickly I was replaced ♪
♪And are you thinking of me when you fuck her? ♪
♪'Cause the love that you gave that we made ♪
♪wasn't able to make it enough for you to be open wide, ♪
♪no ♪
♪And every time you speak her name ♪
♪Does she know how you told me you'd hold me ♪
♪Until you died, 'til you died ♪
♪But you're still alive ♪
♪And I'm here ♪
♪to remind you ♪
♪Of the mess you left when you went away ♪
♪It's not fair ♪
♪to deny me ♪
♪Of the cross I bear that you gave to me ♪
♪You, you, you oughta know ♪
♪Ooh ♪
♪Ah ♪
♪No ♪
♪'Cause the joke that you laid in the bed that was me ♪
♪And I'm not gonna fade ♪
♪As soon as you close your eyes, and you know it ♪
♪And every time I scratch my nails down someone else's back ♪
♪I hope you feel it...well, can you feel it ♪
♪Well I'm here ♪
♪to remind you ♪
♪Of the mess you left when you went away ♪
♪It's not fair ♪
♪to deny me ♪
♪Of the cross I bear that you gave to me ♪
♪You, you, you oughta know ♪
♪I'm here ♪
♪to remind you ♪
♪Of the mess you left when you went away ♪
♪It's not fair ♪
♪to deny me ♪
♪Of the cross I bear that you gave to me ♪
♪You, you, you oughta know ♪